Welcome instead of tax, tell me your name sir, at least
once the market direction update and
where were you yesterday, this is the time to open the
bank, the wrapped girl will improve, Bank Nifty has increased by 6 points
and people are always wondering what happened, what happened, the
deal of those who are dying has not been removed and it will not be removed even now, sir, the
expiry on Thursday will be above 25000,
maybe more than that and you have a
chance to take part Amitabh,
tie yourself up a little, don't
look at what is on TV, go John Wick Shopping
and India Jin 10 meter sports pistol
time is in, you should look at the city sales, you should look at the auto
sales, you should look at the cement sales, that is
the place because the update is that your bank
Kotak Bank is up by 155 rupees today from yesterday's price,
so there was a very plated return in it, I gave
you two calls in the morning, ACC and Ambuja Ambuja
44 is Rs.55 and AC Raj 14 15 16
Police is 1665, so
book profit in both of them, apart from that it will give you a big profit
512 13 that is 525 HDFC Life
Line and Godrej Properties also hit their target
1030 so my deduction
is clear sir benefits want to leave from
different low rate low oil is home taken what
transfer Indian markets and dark
stranger trending comedy wala
declines to all remakes but good lines now if you
say 222 header start flight mode then I will
tell painting both brothers today cement
so while commenting both such issues
both
are subscribed so the first brother is Bombay Art in
Pharma result will be very good and bad like
share is allegation and Abhinav Bindra has
just given his diet Mann Ki Baat take it for 17.78
I am fond of 72 I see tomorrow's price of 825 to 840 because
of expiry and the
donkey news from which can come from this
company the second one will be you saw that the insurance
company's leading from the front
ICICI Prudential 412 13 has a stoploss of four to
five eight  There is a song of 400, 450 and 440, I have to wait
for the target of 440, I have to
buy in ICICI Prudential and I have to
buy in Arvindo Pharma
ESI, both of these are on each other's side and
keep 772 subscribe 825 and subscribe